<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>BiohackMax 2024</title>
    <description>Max&apos;s Journey with Biohack Academy 2024</description>
    <link>http://localhost:4000</link>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:4000/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
      <item>
        <title>Building an AI-Integrated Mushroom Incubator</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;The &lt;strong&gt;TastyMushroomIncubator&lt;/strong&gt; project is an ambitious endeavor to create a sophisticated mushroom incubator. The project is planned in three stages, evolving from a miniature prototype to a full-size, AI-powered environmental control system.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;table-of-contents&quot;&gt;Table of Contents&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;#introduction&quot;&gt;Introduction&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;#project-stages&quot;&gt;Project Stages&lt;/a&gt;
    &lt;ul&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;#stage-1-miniature-mushroom-incubator-design-and-assembly&quot;&gt;Stage 1: Miniature Mushroom Incubator Design and Assembly&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;#stage-2-full-size-incubator--plant-grower&quot;&gt;Stage 2: Full-Size Incubator / Plant Grower&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;#stage-3-ai-integration-for-automated-environmental-control&quot;&gt;Stage 3: AI Integration for Automated Environmental Control&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;/ul&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;#inspiration&quot;&gt;Inspiration&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;#implementation-and-testing&quot;&gt;Implementation and Testing&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;#progression&quot;&gt;Project Progress&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;#conclusion&quot;&gt;Conclusion&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;project-stages&quot;&gt;Project Stages&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;stage-1-miniature-mushroom-incubator-design-and-assembly&quot;&gt;Stage 1: Miniature Mushroom Incubator Design and Assembly&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Materials and Components:&lt;/strong&gt; Utilize clear acrylic for visibility and ease of monitoring, with precision cuts made by a laser cutter.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Assembly:&lt;/strong&gt; Detailed design using CAD software for optimal airflow and light distribution, followed by assembly of cut acrylic panels.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;stage-2-full-size-incubator--plant-grower&quot;&gt;Stage 2: Full-Size Incubator / Plant Grower&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Scaling Up:&lt;/strong&gt; Refine the design based on lessons learned from the miniature prototype, using clear acrylic material for the full-size version.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Environmental Control Systems:&lt;/strong&gt; Integration of heating pads and temperature sensors for even heat distribution and accurate temperature monitoring.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;stage-3-ai-integration-for-automated-environmental-control&quot;&gt;Stage 3: AI Integration for Automated Environmental Control&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Electronics and Sensors:&lt;/strong&gt; Installation of temperature sensors, heating pads, cameras, NPK sensors and IR sensors for comprehensive monitoring and control.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;AI System Development:&lt;/strong&gt; Collection of data on growth conditions for the development of an AI model to automatically adjust environment parameters.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;inspiration&quot;&gt;Inspiration&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Inspired by similar projects and products, the journey began with designing the incubator, experimenting with different tools and materials, and gradually integrating electronics for temperature control.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/BiohackMax/images/Incubator-inspiration.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Incubator inspiration&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;implementation-and-testing&quot;&gt;Implementation and Testing&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Prototype Testing:&lt;/strong&gt; Each version of the incubator is thoroughly tested, from the miniature model to the full-scale AI-integrated system.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Calibration and Safety Measures:&lt;/strong&gt; Ensuring the accuracy, reliability, and safety of the incubator system.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;By methodically following this roadmap, the project aims to leverage modern technology for creating optimal growth conditions for mushrooms, showcasing the power of DIY and technological innovation.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Box specs:
Should be made of clear acrylic which we can cut with the laser cutter. Should be 1.4m in height, 0.6m in width and 0.6m in length.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Size of electronic components:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/BiohackMax/images/datasheet-for-temp-sensor.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;datasheet for temp sensor.jpg&quot; width=&quot;250&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h1 id=&quot;temperature-sensor&quot;&gt;Temperature sensor:&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Length: 48.5mm&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Width: 40mm&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Height: 15.15mm&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;h1 id=&quot;heating-pads&quot;&gt;Heating pads:&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Length: 200mm&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Width: 60mm&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Power: USB&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;roadmap&quot;&gt;Roadmap&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Based on the project documentation for your “TastyMushroomIncubator,” it’s clear you’ve meticulously planned the stages of development for an advanced mushroom incubator that will eventually incorporate AI for environmental control. Starting with a small-scale prototype allows for thorough testing and refinement before scaling up, which is a wise approach. Let’s outline a roadmap tailored to your project’s specifications and stages.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;stage-1-miniature-mushroom-incubator-design-and-assembly-1&quot;&gt;Stage 1: Miniature Mushroom Incubator Design and Assembly&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&quot;materials-and-components&quot;&gt;Materials and Components&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Acrylic Sheets:&lt;/strong&gt; Utilize clear acrylic for visibility and easy monitoring. Your dimensions suggest a significant size, but start with a scaled-down model if this is the initial prototype.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Laser Cutter:&lt;/strong&gt; Employ the laser cutter for precise cuts and etchings on the acrylic, ensuring perfect fit and assembly.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&quot;assembly&quot;&gt;Assembly&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Design:&lt;/strong&gt; Create a detailed design of the incubator using CAD software, considering the internal layout for optimal airflow and light distribution.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Cutting:&lt;/strong&gt; Use the laser cutter to cut the acrylic panels based on your design. Include slots for easy assembly and areas for inserting the electronic components.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Assembly:&lt;/strong&gt; Assemble the cut panels using acrylic glue or screws designed for acrylic, ensuring stability and airtightness where necessary.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;stage-2-full-size-incubator--plant-grower-1&quot;&gt;Stage 2: Full-Size Incubator / Plant Grower&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&quot;scaling-up&quot;&gt;Scaling Up&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Take lessons learned from the miniature prototype to refine the design.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Maintain the clear acrylic material for the full-size version, ensuring that the larger panels are supported adequately to prevent bending or breaking.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&quot;environmental-control-systems&quot;&gt;Environmental Control Systems&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Integrate the heating pads and temperature sensors, ensuring even distribution of heat and accurate temperature monitoring throughout the incubator.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;stage-3-ai-integration-for-automated-environmental-control-1&quot;&gt;Stage 3: AI Integration for Automated Environmental Control&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&quot;electronics-and-sensors&quot;&gt;Electronics and Sensors&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Temperature Sensors:&lt;/strong&gt; Install these for precise climate control, considering the size and placement for accurate readings.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Heating Pads:&lt;/strong&gt; Strategically place the heating pads to provide uniform warmth, powered via USB for easy adjustments and power management.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Cameras and IR Sensors:&lt;/strong&gt; These will monitor the growth progress and detect any abnormalities in the mushrooms.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;pH Sensors:&lt;/strong&gt; Essential for maintaining the substrate at optimal pH levels for mushroom growth.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&quot;ai-system-development&quot;&gt;AI System Development&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Data Collection:&lt;/strong&gt; Use the sensors and cameras to collect data on growth conditions and mushroom health.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;AI Model:&lt;/strong&gt; Develop or adapt an AI model capable of analyzing the collected data to adjust temperature, lighting, and pH levels automatically. This could involve machine learning algorithms trained on optimal growth conditions for various mushroom species.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Interface:&lt;/strong&gt; Design a user interface for monitoring and manual overrides, ensuring ease of use and accessibility for non-technical users.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&quot;implementation-and-testing-1&quot;&gt;Implementation and Testing&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Prototype Testing:&lt;/strong&gt; Thoroughly test each version of the incubator, starting with the miniature model and progressing through to the full-scale AI-integrated system.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Calibration:&lt;/strong&gt; Calibrate sensors and the AI system using known standards and test runs to ensure accuracy and reliability.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Safety Measures:&lt;/strong&gt; Implement safety features, especially in the full-size model, to protect against overheating or other electrical hazards.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;By following this roadmap, you can systematically develop a sophisticated mushroom incubator that leverages modern technology for optimal growth conditions. Your well-equipped workshops and clear planning position you excellently for success in this ambitious project.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;progression&quot;&gt;Progression&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;To start I looked for inspiration from similar projects and products online. Once I found one I liked (see inspiration) I started looking for options to make the vector graphic file for the cutout. At first I found VectorArt.AI which did not work as intended to form the cutout for my box (see vectai.jpg).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Then I started searching for open libraries similar to Thingiverse but for vector graphics and laser cut projects and found &lt;a href=&quot;https://3axis.co/download/qommv2ro&quot;&gt;3axis.co&lt;/a&gt; (box cutout for 12mm plywood which needed to be adjusted for 6mm).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I then set up my Inkscape to work with .eps files by following these instructions. In the end, this step was unnecessary as the file I got from 3axis.co was a .cdr which opened fine in Inkscape.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I then adjusted the design a bit, scaled to my desired dimensions, and exported the .svg file to the USB stick. I then went to the laser cutter and after setting everything up I noticed that I had to adjust the size of the cutout holes to fit the 3mm plywood.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;After adjusting in Lightburn the laser cutting began and once it was finished I had cutouts for my incubator box. With some help from the team, we assembled the incubator box and I began thinking how to integrate my electronics (mainly the temperature controller and heating pads).
&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;/BiohackMax/images/box-assembled.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Incubator box assembled&quot; width=&quot;250&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;To do this I uploaded my progress including images of the box, electronics, and PDF manual for the electronics into a DIY GPT to figure out what challenges and possible solutions I could face.
&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;/BiohackMax/images/upload-project-parts-to-chatgpt.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Uploading project parts to ChatGPT&quot; width=&quot;250&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Since the datasheet for the temperature controller was in Chinese I wanted to be extra safe and test out first with a bench power supply. Unfortunately I did not have access to one at the time so I constructed my own 12V power source using 2 9V batteries conencted in series to get 12V and converted the voltage to 12V with a buck converter.
&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;/BiohackMax/images/testing-with-2-9v-batteries.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Testing with 2 9V batteries&quot; width=&quot;250&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Unfortunately I thought the controller was rated for 12V input, however it’s operational voltage was 5V, which I realized only after accidentally destroying 3 temperature controllers.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;After finally figuring out the 5V problem and understanding how the relay of the temperature controller works I wired everything up and the heating pads were finally heating up to the set temperature.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I then assembled the box and electronics to make sure everything works and fits together.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/BiohackMax/images/Incubator-box-with-electronics-not-complete.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Box assembled with working electronics&quot; width=&quot;250&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Satisfied with how everything fits together I started thinking of a more permanent fixture, however I did not want to use glue in case I would want to disassemble and reassemble the incubator later.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Since I did not have a lot of time as we were supposed to present the next day I decided to 3D print only 2 &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.thingiverse.com/thing:38277&quot;&gt;triple corner joints&lt;/a&gt; (to connect the backboard) and use 2 metal corner brackets that I found in the lab.
&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;/BiohackMax/images/3d-printed-triple-corner-joints.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;3D printer triple corner joints&quot; width=&quot;250&quot; /&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;/BiohackMax/images/box-with-joints.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Box with corner joints&quot; width=&quot;250&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 25 Mar 2024 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/Building-an-AI-Integrated-Mushroom-Incubator/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/Building-an-AI-Integrated-Mushroom-Incubator/</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Lecture 1 - Biosafety</title>
        <description>&lt;h2 id=&quot;exploring-biosafety-and-laboratory-protocols&quot;&gt;Exploring Biosafety and Laboratory Protocols&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Welcome to our latest installment of lab notes from the Biohack Academy! In this post, we’ll be delving into the essentials of biosafety, laboratory protocols, and collaborative efforts discussed during our recent meeting. From risk assessment strategies to the importance of international standards, join us as we navigate through key insights and reminders shared by Per Staugaard and fellow participants. Let’s dive in!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;-risk-assessment-and-mitigation-measures&quot;&gt;🔬 Risk Assessment and Mitigation Measures&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The effectiveness of mitigation measures for polio viruses is between 60 and 75%. Mitigation measures should be taken at different levels, with the most effective being the source material worked with. Technical measures and organizational measures should be implemented to reduce risk to an acceptable level. Risk assessments should be done for every organism and appropriate mitigation measures should be taken.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;-laboratory-safety-and-hygiene&quot;&gt;🧪 Laboratory Safety and Hygiene&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Personal protection and safe behavior are emphasized. Handwashing is important for maintaining hygiene. Labeling of materials is necessary, including names, dates, and contents. Safety data sheets should be known and followed. Waste should be properly disposed of. Glass should be handled carefully to avoid sharp points. Materials should not be mixed if they can react with each other.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;-lab-procedures-and-regulations&quot;&gt;🚦 Lab Procedures and Regulations&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Per Staugaard emphasized the importance of following lab rules and SOPs. A small test will be conducted before entering the lab. A permit is required for certain experiments, and the lab must comply with local legislation. Proper labeling of dangerous materials, following international standards, is essential. Materials brought into the lab should be accounted for and removed afterward.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;-clarification-and-questions&quot;&gt;❓ Clarification and Questions&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Per Staugaard encouraged participants to ask questions if they are unsure about procedures or safety measures. He highlighted the importance of clear communication and labeling for shared items. The lab manager’s tasks, lab setup, waste disposal, and safety procedures were discussed. The European directive should be translated into local legislation, ensuring consistency in regulations.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;-international-collaboration-and-standardization&quot;&gt;🌍 International Collaboration and Standardization&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The importance of international standards and collaboration was mentioned. Different countries may have variations in their regulations and implementation.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;-ideas-for-future-discussion&quot;&gt;💡 Ideas for Future Discussion&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The topic of Ebola research and how to conduct it was brought up. The discussion of a similar topic was suggested for future meetings.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;-meeting-logistics&quot;&gt;📝 Meeting Logistics&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The meeting was recorded. A follow-up test was mentioned. The need for proper training and following instructions from trainers/instructors was emphasized.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;-participant-engagement&quot;&gt;👤 Participant Engagement&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Participants were encouraged to actively engage and ask questions during the meeting.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;-repetition-and-reminder&quot;&gt;🔁 Repetition and Reminder&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Per Staugaard reiterated certain points, such as handwashing and labeling.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;-confidentiality-and-safety&quot;&gt;🔒 Confidentiality and Safety&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Initially, there was hesitation about sharing information about polio virus safety, but it was ultimately decided to share it with the world.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;️-cleanliness-and-waste-disposal&quot;&gt;🗑️ Cleanliness and Waste Disposal&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The importance of keeping the lab clean and disposing of waste properly was emphasized.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;additional-notes&quot;&gt;Additional Notes:&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Pathogenicity is the capacity of an organism to cause disease. During virus infections, diseases symptoms arise from two causes, direct injury caused by virus replication and the side effects of the immune response to infection. The balance between these two is variable.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Alimentary tract: The organs that food and liquids travel through when they are swallowed, digested, absorbed, and leave the body as feces. These organs include the mouth, pharynx (throat), esophagus, stomach, small intestine, large intestine, rectum, and anus.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The conjunctiva is a thin, clear membrane that protects your eye. It covers the inside of your eyelid and the white of your eye (the sclera). The conjunctiva creates the mucus layer that forms part of your tears.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Aerosol means dissolved in air - smaller than 10 microns.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;An aerosol may be defined as a suspension of particles or droplets in the air and includes airborne dusts, mists, fumes or smoke. Suspended particle sizes may range from a few nanometers to hundreds of micrometers in diameter and particles can be manufactured or naturally occurring.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Level of measures you take is based on the risk assessment and you can then take mitigation methods based on that.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.cdc.gov/brucellosis/laboratories/risk-level.html&quot;&gt;Link to CDC Brucellosis Laboratories Risk Level&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;PEP - post exposure procedure&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;An autoclave is a machine that uses steam under pressure to kill harmful bacteria, viruses, fungi, and spores on items that are placed inside a pressure vessel. The items are heated to an appropriate sterilization temperature for a given amount of time.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We wear a labcoat because it changes your mindset when you change clothes and enter the lab.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://docs.google.com/document/d/1LbO1qIUcXun85iCY1ZSKHKBBaLF8jPIVQ2HS-JsG1aY/edit?usp=sharing&quot;&gt;Link to Document&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/weissman.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Bra[2016-2-23-Hello-World.md](2016-2-23-Hello-World.md)inbow&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 25 Mar 2024 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/lecture-1-biosafety/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/lecture-1-biosafety/</guid>
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>